<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SmartNFCTag</string>
    <string name="set_alaram_001">SET_ALAR@M_001</string>
    <string name="silient_phone_002">SILIENT-PH#NE_002</string>
    <string name="make_call_003">enMAKE-CALL_003</string>
    <string name="navigate_app_004">NAVIGATE_APP_004</string>
    <string name="send_sms_005">SEND-SMS_005</string>
    <string name="wifi_off_006">WIFI_OFF_006</string>
    <string name="find_address_007">FIND-ADDR3SS_007</string>
    <string name="screen_bright_008">SCREEN-BRIGHT_008</string>
    <string name="read_doc_009">READ-DOC_009</string>
    <string name="read_message_010">READ-MESSAGE_010</string>
    <string name="social_media_011">SOCIAL-MEDIA_011</string>
    <string name="share_contact_012">SHARE-CONTACT_012</string>
    <string name="master_key_Tag">MASTER_KEY</string>
    <string name="default_i_013">DEFAULT-i_013</string>

    <string name="write"><b>NFC Technology: Unlocking Powerful Possibilities. </b> \n\nNear Field Communication (NFC) is a powerful technology that allows
        seamless data transfer between devices. With an Android phone, you can easily write information to NFC stickers,
        enabling quick and efficient sharing of data. Here are some key points to consider \n\nConvenience: NFC stickers can store various types of data, such as URLs, contact information, and text messages, making them versatile for different applications.\nEase of Use: Writing to NFC stickers is straightforward and can be done with just a few taps on your Android phone.\nSecurity: NFC technology includes encryption features, ensuring that the data transferred is secure and protected.\nAutomation: NFC stickers can trigger actions on your phone, such as opening apps or changing settings, enhancing your daily routines.\nCompatibility: Most modern Android phones support NFC, making it accessible to a wide range of users.\nInnovation: NFC technology continues to evolve, offering new and exciting possibilities for personal and professional use.\n</string>
    <string name="read"><b>Enable NFC on Your Phone: </b> Go to your phone\'s
    settings and ensure that NFC is turned on. This is usually found under \"Connections\" or Wireless and Networks.\n\n <b>Open an NFC Reader App:</b> Launch an NFC reader app on your phone. Many Android phones come h a built-in NFC reader,
        or you can download one from the Google Play Store.\n\n<b>Tap the NFC Tag:</b> Hold the back of your phone close to the NFC tag.
        Your phone will automatically detect and read the information stored on the tag, displaying it on your screen.</string>
    <string name="overwrite"><b>Enable NFC and Install an NFC Writing App:</b>\n Ensure that NFC is enabled on your phone by going to the settings and turning it on.
        Download and install an NFC writing app from the Google Play Store,
        such as NFC Tools or NXP TagWriter.\n\n<b>Prepare the Data to Write: </b>Open the NFC writing app and select the type of data you want to write to the NFC tag, such as a URL,
        text, or contact information. Enter the data in the app.\n\n<b>Write to the NFC Tag:</b> Hold the NFC tag close to the back of your phone. Follow the app\'s instructions to write the data to the tag. The app will confirm once the writing process is complete.</string>

    <string name="navigate_apps_instrution">Enable NFC from Settings → Connections (or Network and Internet) and turn it on. Make sure the NFC tag is properly programmed and placed in an accessible spot. Hold your device near the tag, align the NFC sensor, and wait for detection. Your device should automatically open the app—confirm if prompted.
        \n Follow on-screen instructions and grant permissions if needed. \n\n\n <b> Navigate to Youtube app to Play Android Video.</b> </string>
    <string name="wifi_off_on">Enable NFC from Settings → Connections (or Network and Internet) and turn it on. Make sure the NFC tag is properly programmed and placed in an accessible spot.
        Hold your device near the tag, align the NFC sensor, and wait for detection.
        Your device should automatically open the app—confirm if prompted.
        \n **Instructions to Enable NFC and Control Silent Mode:**

1. **Enable NFC:** Go to your device\'s settings, select "Connections" or "Network and Internet," and enable NFC.
2. **Grant Permissions:** Ensure the app has the necessary permissions to modify sound settings and use NFC.
3. **Prepare NFC Tag:** Make sure the NFC tag is properly programmed and positioned for easy access.
4. **Tap NFC Tag:** Hold your device close to the NFC tag, aligning the NFC sensor with the tag.
5. **Control Silent Mode:** Once the NFC tag is scanned, tap the button to switch between silent mode on and off.  </string>
    <string name="bright_low_high">Step 1: Add a SeekBar to your layout for adjusting screen brightness.\nStep 2: Use window attributes to modify the screen brightness based on the SeekBar value, ranging from minimum to maximum brightness.\nStep 3: Update the screen brightness dynamically as the SeekBar value changes.</string>
    <string name="sms_send"><![CDATA["**Instructions for Sending SMS Using NFC:**  \n\n1. **Enable NFC:** Go to your device's settings, select \"Connections\" or \"Network & Internet,\" and enable NFC.  \n2. **Grant SMS Permission:** Ensure the app has permission to send SMS. If prompted, allow the permission.  \n3. **Prepare the NFC Tag:** Make sure the NFC tag is properly configured and within reach.  \n4. **Position Your Device:** Hold your device close to the NFC tag, ensuring the NFC sensor aligns with the tag.  \n5. **Confirmation:** Once the NFC tag is scanned, the pre-configured SMS will be sent automatically to the specified number.  "]]></string>
    <string name="wifi_instruction">"Starting from Android 10 (API 29), Google restricted the ability to programmatically enable or disable Wi-Fi due to privacy and security reasons. "</string>
    <string name="PDF_read_Instruction"><b>Instruction Page </b> Step 1: Enable NFC**  \n- Open your phone\'s **Settings**.  \n- Go to **Connections** → **NFC and Contactless Payments**.  \n- Toggle the switch to **enable NFC**.  \n\n**Step 2: Scan the NFC Tag**  \n- Hold the back of your phone near the NFC tag.  \n- When the phone detects the tag, a notification will appear.  \n\n**Step 3: Open the PDF Document**  \n- The tag will contain a URL.  \n- Tap the notification to open the URL.  \n- The linked PDF document will open automatically. </string>
    <string name="location_instruction">"### **Steps to Load and Display Current Location on Google Maps via NFC**  \n\n1. **Tap the NFC Tag** – Open the app and tap the NFC tag.  \n2. **Get Location** – The app will request location permission (if needed) and fetch the current latitude and longitude.  \n3. **Open Google Maps** – The app creates a `geo:` URI and launches Google Maps.  \n4. **Show Location** – Google Maps will display a pin at the fetched location.  \n5. **Error Handling** – If permissions are denied or Google Maps is unavailable, an error message will be shown.  "</string>
    <string name="set_alarm_text"><b>Instructions: </b> \n1. **Enable NFC:**  \n   - Open **Settings** → **Connected Devices** → Enable **NFC**.  \n\n2. **Set Alarm After 5 Minutes:**  \n   - Tap the NFC tag.  \n   - The app will set an alarm 5 minutes from the current time.  \n   - A notification with a stop button will appear.  \n\n3. **Set Alarm at Custom Time:**  \n   - Tap **Set Custom Alarm** button.  \n   - Select a time using the time picker.  \n   - The alarm will trigger at the selected time.</string>
    <string name="readMessage">### **Instruction Page**  \n\n**Step 1: Enable NFC**  \n- Open your phone\'s **Settings**.  \n- Go to **Connections** → **NFC and Contactless Payments**.  \n- Toggle the switch to **enable NFC**.  \n\n**Step 2: Scan the NFC Tag**  \n- Hold the back of your phone near the NFC tag.  \n- When the phone detects the tag, a notification will appear.  \n\n**Step 3: Open the Message Document**  \n- The tag will contain a URL.  \n- Tap the notification to open the URL.  \n- The linked PDF document will open automatically.</string>
    <string name="share_contact_content"><![CDATA[📱 Steps for Sharing a Contact via NFC in the Android App\nConfigure the Contact on the NFC Tag\n\nThe NFC tag must be programmed with a contact (vCard format or plain text with contact details).\n\nEnable NFC on Your Device\n\nGo to Settings > Connections > NFC and turn it ON if it\'s not already enabled.\n\nOpen the App\n\nLaunch the Android app that supports scanning and sharing contacts.\n\nScan the NFC Tag\n\nGently tap the back of your phone on the NFC tag.\n\nThe app will automatically detect the NFC tag and read the configured contact information.\n\nView the Contact Details\n\nOnce scanned, the contact details will be displayed on the screen.\n\nChoose to Share the Contact\n\nA Share button will be visible under the contact details.\n\nSelect an App to Share\n\nAfter tapping the Share button:\n\nA list of apps (Messenger, WhatsApp, Gmail, SMS, etc.) will pop up.\n\nSelect the app you want to use for sharing.\n\nSend the Contact\n\nThe contact information will be attached to the selected app.\n\nYou can now choose the recipient and send the contact easily.]]></string>
</resources>